John H. Cornehlsen Papers 5730
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III: Office Files
  - Sub-Series B: Teaching
    - Interview Training: How to Stimulate Frank Discussion During the Interview (Box 55, Folder 4)
      Handout no.12
    - Interview Training: Interpreting and Evaluating Interview Data (Box 55, Folder 5)
      Handout no.13
    - Interview Training: Some Tested Questions (Box 55, Folder 6)
      Handout no.25
    - Interview Training: Interview Fact Sheet (Box 55, Folder 7)
      Handout no.27
    - Interview Training: John Wiley Fact Sheet, "Questions" Case (Box 55, Folder 8)
      Handout no.29
    - Interview Training: College Recruiting Interviewing (Box 55, Folder 9)
      Handout no.30
    - Interview Training: Interview Practice Case A: John Richards Resume, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Interview Training: How to Get Others to Talk (Box 55, Folder 11)
      Handout no.40
    - Interview Training: Course Evaluations, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Interview Seminar, Union Carbide: Course Evaluations (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Management II: Course Evaluations, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Management 22: Course Evaluations, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Management 270, Executive Leadership: Selected Reading List (Box 55, Folder 16)
      Three page reading list, includes prices.
    - Management 502: Course Evaluations, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Management 647: Course Evaluations, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Management 647: Course Evaluations, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Management 670 and 670, Executive Leadership and Supervision: Selected Reading List (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Management 670: Course Evaluations, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Management 670: Course Evaluations, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Management 670: Course Evaluations, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Management 671: Executive Potential Analysis, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 24)
      Syllabus.
    - Management 671: Management Development Survey (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Management 671: Course Evaluations, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Management 671: Course Evaluations, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Management Motivation Seminar, Unit 4 (Box 55, Folder 28)
      Handouts.
    - Occupational Counseling and Career Development: Bibliography (Box 55, Folder 29)
      Five page bibliography organized by subject.
    - Occupational Counseling and Career Development: Course Evaluations, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Occupational Counseling and Career Development: Course Evaluations, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Personal Career Assessment: Course Evaluations (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - Personality Testing: Course Notes (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - Psychology I, Social Psychology: Population Control (Box 55, Folder 34)
      Group Discussion Outline no.5
    - Psychology I, Social Psychology: Politics and Personality (Box 55, Folder 35)
      Group Discussion Outline no.6
    - Psychology I, Social Psychology: Environment and Urban Life (Box 55, Folder 36)
      Group Discussion Outline no.7
    - Psychology I, Social Psychology: Race and Race Prejudice (Box 55, Folder 37)
      Group Discussion Outline no.8
    - Psychology I, Social Psychology: Violence (Box 55, Folder 38)
    - Psychology I, Social Psychology: Community (Box 55, Folder 39)
      Group Discussion Outline no.9
    - Psychology I, Social Psychology: Why People Like Each Other (Box 55, Folder 40)
      Group Discussion Outline no.10
    - Psychology I, Social Psychology: Notes [folder 1 of 2], 1970 (Box 55, Folder 41)
    - Psychology I, Social Psychology: Notes [folder 2 of 2], 1970 (Box 55, Folder 42)
    - Psychology I, Social Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 43)
    - Psychology II: "Critical Incident" Essays (Box 55, Folder 44)
      Essays written by students about an incident that shaped their lifes.
    - Psychology II: Course Evalutations, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 45)
    - Psychology II: Course Evalutations, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 46)
    - Psychology II: Course Evalutations, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 47)
    - Psychology II: Group Discussion Outline no. 3: Ethics and Morality, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 48)
    - Psychology III: Course Evalutations, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 49)
    - Psychology 25, Child Psychology: Handouts, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 50)
      Classnotes handout, assignment sheet, and second exam.
    - Psychology 25, Child Psychology: Notes [folder 1 of 2] (Box 55, Folder 51)
    - Psychology 25, Child Psychology: Notes [folder 2 of 2] (Box 55, Folder 52)
    - Psychology 25, Child Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 53)
    - Psychology 25, Child Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 54)
    - Psychology 25, Child Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 55)
    - Psychology 25, Child Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 56)
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Syllabus and Bibliography, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 57)
      Two page syllabus and a nine page bibliography.
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Chapter Study Guides (Box 55, Folder 58)
      For Erik Erikson's "Identity, Youth and Crisis"
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Attitudes Toward Sexual Freedom, 1973-1974 (Box 55, Folder 59)
      Handout for Topic 1.
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Personal Adjustment (Box 55, Folder 60)
      Group Discussion Outline no.3
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Family Adjustment (Box 55, Folder 61)
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Effects of Family on Behavior (Box 55, Folder 62)
      Group Discussion Outline.
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Exam, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 63)
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Notes, 1964-1967 (Box 55, Folder 64)
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Notes, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 65)
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Lecture Notes [folder 1 of 2], 1973 (Box 55, Folder 66)
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Lecture Notes [folder 2 of 2], 1973 (Box 55, Folder 67)
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 68)
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 69)
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 70)
    - Psychology 26, Adolescent Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Psychology 32, Social Psychology: Syllabus, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      Syllabus and attendance sheets.
    - Psychology 32, Social Psychology: Notes, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Psychology 32, Social Psychology: Sex and Sex Discrimination, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      Group Discussion Outline no.1.
    - Psychology 32, Social Psychology: Protest and Social Action, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      Group Discussion Outline no.2.
    - Psychology 32, Social Psychology: Education, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      Group Discussion Outline no.3.
    - Psychology 32, Social Psychology: Communication, Propaganda, and Persuasion (Box 56, Folder 7)
      Group Discussion Outline no.10.
    - Psychology 32, Social Psychology: Self-Justification (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Psychology 32, Social Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Psychology 32, Social Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Psychology 32, Social Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Psychology 32, Social Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Psychology 47, Industrial Psychology: Notes on Edward Strong's "Psychology" (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Handwritten notes on 5x8 index cards.
    - Psychology 47, Industrial Psychology: Final Exam, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      Ten short-answer or essay questions.
    - Psychology 47, Industrial Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Psychology 47, Industrial Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1968 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Psychology 47, Industrial Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Psychology 47, Industrial Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Psychology 47, Industrial Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Psychology 47, Industrial Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Psychology 48: Course Evaluations, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Psychology 63, Abnormal Psychology: Final Exam, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      Fifty multiple-choice questions
    - Psychology 63, Abnormal Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Psychology 63, Abnormal Psychology: Course Evaluations, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Psycholgy 187, Personnel Seminar: Market Research and Its Application, 1955 (Box 56, Folder 25)
      Term paper by a student
    - Psychology 526, Sections D and E: Objective Questions, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 26)
      Exam with 102 multiple-choice questions. One blank exam and one completed exam.
    - Psychology 526: Student Term Papers (Box 56, Folder 27)
      Five student papers with Dr. Cornehlsen's comments.
    - Understanding Human Behavior in Industry and Business: Course Evaluations, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Film Catalogs (Box 56, Folder 29)
      Catalogs from American Societ for Training and Development, Guidance Associates, and Psychology Today.
    - Catalog of Assessment and Develepment Exercises, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 30)
      Guidance Associates.
  - Sub-Series C: Personal
    - Cornehlsen Resumes (Box 56, Folder 31)
      Several iterations.
    - Personal (Box 56, Folder 32)
      Miscellaneous correspondence, certificates, etc.
    - Christmas Card List (Box 56, Folder 33)
      Cards and notes.
    - Cornehlsen and Associates Checking Account, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 34)
      Statements and cancelled checks.
    - John H. Cornehlsen Checking Account, 1961 (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Special Checking Account, 1960-1961 (Box 56, Folder 36)
      Receipts.
    - Regular Checking Account, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Consulting Bills, 1953-1954 (Box 56, Folder 38)
      Bills for materials and services Dr. Cornehlsen used for consulting. Includes cancelled checks.
    - Account Book, 1958-1960 (Box 56, Folder 39)
      Accounts for Dr. Cornehlsen's consulting business.
    - Account Book, 1960-1962 (Box 56, Folder 40)
    - Account Book, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 41)
    - Account Book: Houghton-Mifflin (Box 56, Folder 42)
      Record of royalties received for publication of tests.
    - Tuition Survey Data, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 43)
      Notes and correspondence regarding a survey of college and university tuition assistance for the children of employees.
    - Great Neck Community Forum, 1957-1959 (Box 56, Folder 44)
    - Great Neck Junior High School PTA, 1956-1957 (Box 56, Folder 45)
      Correspondence and handwritten notes.
    - Index (Box 56, Folder 46)
      Alphabetical index to an unknown book.
    - Photographs (Box 56, Folder 47)
      Three black and white photographs.